GIRISH PATHAK

web designer

Experience designing and programming web pages. Strong understanding of aesthetic and design principalsExcellent troubleshooting and bug resolutions abilitiesCritical thinking and problem-solving skillsEvaluation and analysis abilitiesExcellent communication skills, including written and verbalStrong attention to small details



pathakgirish239@gmail.com

+91 7772001067

thaltej, Ahmedabad

EDUCATION

BCA

Prestige Institute Of Management, Gwalior

06/2020 - Present

Courses

 Software Development, Web-Based Applications, Software Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web designer-internship Zoxhins group of India Pvt. Ltd.

05/2019 - 05/2020

Web designer

Metizsoft Solutions Private Limited, Ahmedabad

06/2020 - Present

SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3 bootstrap 4.6

PERSONAL PROJECTS

https://www.metizsoft.com/hire-node-js-developers/

this websit design by me

https://www.metizsoft.com/hire-react-js-developers/

this websit design by me

https://homekitcheninc.com/

this websit design by me

https://www.metizsoft.com/hire-react-nativedevelopers/

this websit design by me

CERTIFICATES

web design diploma

TGC institute awalior

ACHIEVEMENTS

Achievement Name

LANGUAGES

Hindi Full Professional Proficiency English

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Gaming Learning languages Photography Traveling Sports yoga Reading Listening to music watch movie driving